http://www.oxsci.com/privacy-policy/

Contact
MY SPECSPrivacy PolicyCopyrightAll information and the structure of the SPECS websites are protected by Copyright and/or trade mark right. Any other intellectual property rights are also protected by law for the respective right holder even if not specifically marked as being so protected. The duplication or dissemination of structure, information or data, in particular the use of text, extracts from texts or pictures, graphics, videos etc. requires the prior agreement of SPECS except for the contact addresses and all information provided under the link „Press“, which may be reproduced.ActualityBefore posting any information on its website, SPECS makes reasonable efforts to carefully examine and update its content. Despite all the care taken, data could have changed in the meantime, therefore no responsibility or guarantee can be taken that the information made available is always up-to-date, is correct and complete nor that such information is free from any third party intellectual property rights or copyrights. A liability of SPECS for any damage whatsoever which has been caused by the use or non-use of the information provided on this website, or by the use of inaccurate or incomplete information provided hereon, is hereby excluded. SPECS reserves the right to modify, enhance, or cancel any of the pages or offers made, in whole or in part, without prior notice.Bindingness / Contractual agreementsThe information on the website of SPECS may contain specifications or general descriptions of technical characteristics of products. If a user of the website of SPECS should enter into a contract on products which are described or depicted on this website, only the specifications agreed between the user and SPECS in such a contract will be binding. All offers on SPECS websites are non-binding and without any obligation.LinksOur websites contain links to other sites on the internet and to apps. The following shall apply to each of our links: We expressly declare that we have no influence nor impact on the content of the linked sites. Therefore and herewith we explicitly dissociate from each and any content of linked sites. Should any infringement caused by the external website come to the attention of SPECS, SPECS will immediately delete the link. SPECS does not have any responsibility for the availability of such external website or for its content.Social MediaSocial plug-ins from FacebookWe use social plug-ins from facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plug-ins can be recognized by way of the Facebook logo or the supplement "Facebook Social Plug-in". For example, if you click on the "Like" button or leave a comment, the relevant information is transmitted directly from your browser to Facebook and stored there. Furthermore, Facebook makes your likes public for your Facebook friends. If you are logged into Facebook, it can assign the invocation of our page directly to your Facebook account. Even if you are not logged in or don't have a Facebook account, your browser sends information (e.g. which web pages you have called up, your IP address) which is then stored by Facebook. For details about handling of your personal data by Facebook and your related rights, please refer to the data privacy policy of Facebook: www.facebook.com/policy. If you do not want Facebook to map data collected about you via our Web sites to your Facebook account, you must log out of Facebook before you visit our web pages.Social plug-ins from TwitterWith Twitter and its Retweet functions, we use social plug-ins from Twitter.com, operated by Twitter Inc. 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107. If you use Retweet, the websites visited by you are announced to third parties and associated with your Twitter account. Details about handling of your data by Twitter as well as your rights and setting options for protecting your personal information can be found in Twitter's data privacy policy: www.twitter.com/privacy.Personal dataSPECS GmbH is committed to looking after any personal data it collects about you. This policy explains the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be used, the control you have over your personal data and the procedures we have in place to protect it. It applies to any personal data which is collected and/or provided through our website www.specs.com (the 'Website'). SPECS is the data controller of any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us via the Website. By continuing to use the Website and by submitting information to our Website you are accepting the practices described in this policy. We may revise this policy from time to time and will post any changes on this webpage of the Website. Please check this page regularly to keep up-to-date with any such changes. The Website may contain links to and from other websites, including websites operated by our partners and other third parties. We have no control over any third-party sites that link to or from the Website. If you follow a link to any third-party websites, then please note that they should have their own separate privacy policies. Please check those privacy policies before you use or submit any personal data to third-party websites. We do not accept any liability or responsibility for any third-party websites, the privacy policies applicable to them or their use of the information that they collect from you. While SPECS acts worldwide, all personal information collected,  will be treated in line with the laws applicable in the European Union, regardless of the users country of origin. Any information sent to SPECS from a particular country may be transferred electronically to a server of one of SPECS‘s subsidiaries in another country. Such information could be used, stored, or processed in a country other than the one in which it was generated. Generally, our Internet site can be freely accessed without submitting any personal information. If any of the web pages require the entry of personal data (email address, name, postal address etc.) - for example, for delivering requested brochures - such entry will be entirely voluntary. With regard to requests for information material, offers, or services, SPECS is entitled to distribute the data within the SPECS Group and/or to its business affiliates entrusted with the particular tasks at hand, for purposes of processing.SPECS collects information via its website in two waysInformation you give usContact details such as your name, signature, address, email address and telephone number and the nature of the products or services in which you are interested. These details are collected when you fill in forms on our Website or when corresponding with us by email. It includes information you provide when completing a job application, when you register to attend an event, when you search or interact with our Website and when you report a problem with our Website.Information we collectDuring your use of the Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your visit and the device that you have used to access the Website. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual personally. The information that we may collect includes:the IP address of the device used to access the Website;the internet domain name through which you accessed the Website (which may be, for example, the domain name of your internet service provider or your place of work);the length of your session on the Website;details of the pages visited on the Website and resources accessed;the web browser used by your device to access the Website;your device's operating system; anddetails of any website that provided you with a link to the Website (for example, Google, if you found us using a search engine).How we use your informationThe legal basis for our use of your personal data as described below will be that this information is required for one or more of the legitimate interests described in this policy or the processing is necessary for SPECS to perform a task in the public interest or for SPECS‘s official functions or SPECS have requested and been granted consent from you to process your personal data for the purpose. We may use your personal data as follows:To provide you with the Website, and the content and services made available through it, including to ensure that the Website and its content are presented in the most effective manner for you and your device.To process any requests from you made via our online formsTo contact you for customer satisfaction and impact surveysTo support products or services you have obtained from us.For marketing and market research purposes if you have consented to such useTo personalise and improve your experience of this websiteIn connection with processing a job applicationTo deal with any queries, complaints or problems reported on the WebsiteTo notify you about changes to our serviceChoiceIn most cases you are not obliged to provide any personal data to us but, if you have requested information from us, we will not be able to provide it without certain information, such as your contact details.StorageWe will only keep your personal data for as long as we need to in order to fulfil the relevant purpose(s) it was collected for, as set out above in this privacy policy, and for as long as we are required to keep it by law.Data Security & International TransfersWe maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your personal data against loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take reasonable steps to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. We will not be liable for any loss of or interception of your information, unless this results from our failure to use reasonable steps to keep it secure. Your personal data will not be transferred, or stored, outside of the European Economic Area ('EEA') without your prior written consent.Your rightsYou have a number of rights in relation to how your personal data is used. We have detailed some of your rights below:To ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposesTo access personal data held about you and to obtain a copy of it, including to receive your personal data, which you have provided to SPECS, in a structured, commonly-used and machine readable format and the right to transmit that data to another data controller without hindrance, or to have that personal data transmitted to another data controller, where technically feasibleTo obtain without undue delay the rectification or completion of personal data which are inaccurate or incompleteTo restrict or object to the processing of your personal data and to request its erasure under certain circumstancesIf you would like to obtain a written copy of your personal data or if you need to amend any of your personal details, please write to us at the address detailed under the Contact Us section.To request your personal data you will be asked to verify your identity and specify what information you require and provide us with details of an address to which we should send the information.If you would like to ask us not to send you further marketing communications at any time. You can do so by contacting us using the details in the Contact Us section below. Each marketing email we send to you will also include an option for you to opt out of further marketing emails.CookiesWhen you visit the SPECS website, if your browser is using the standard settings and it is accepting cookies, you are giving consent for cookies on the SPECS site to be stored on your computer. If you do not wish for this to happen, you can disable them in the settings of your browser. The SPECS website may use cookies. Cookies are small, text-only strings of data which store information on the hard drive of your local computer or mobile device. Some cookies store data just for the time you are on the site. These are called session cookies and are not stored on your computer after you have left the site. Most internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies but if you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you when they are being used.Open Cookie Consent Manager / Edit Cookie SettingsGoogle AnalyticsThis website uses functions of Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics also uses so-called cookies, i.e. text files which are stored on your computer and which help analyze how you use the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website will usually be transmitted to and stored by Google on a server in the United States. However, if IP anonymization is activated on this website, your IP address is shortened by Google in the member states of the European Union or in other countries which are signatories to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is transmitted to Google servers in the United States and then shortened. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your utilization of the website, to prepare reports about the activities on the website and to provide additional services to the operator of the website related to the utilization of the website and the use of the internet. You may refuse the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser software; however, please note that in this case you may not be able to use the full functionality of the website.You may also prevent the collection of the data referring to you that are generated by the cookie (including your IP address) in relation to the use of the website and the subsequent transfer to Google and the processing of these data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enIn Addition or alternative to the browser-add-on you can prevent Google Analytics from collecting your data by clicking on the following link . This sets an opt-out cookie that prevents the collection of your data during any future visits to our websites. Deactivate Google Analytics. You can find further information about how Google Analytics handles user data in Google’s Data Protection Policy at: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=de . Blocking of access rightsSPECS is entitled to cancel access rights at any time by blocking the access codes, without obligation or an explanation thereto. This applies in particular if the user is in violation of these Conditions of Use or is not conscientious in handling the data or has provided false statements when registering or has not accessed the site for an extended period of time.VirusesAlthough constantly striving to protect its website against viruses, SPECS cannot guarantee that its website is completely virus-free. Therefore, the users are recommended to take appropriate safety measures themselves.Other provisionsShould one or more of the provisions herein or parts thereof be declared invalid or unenforceable, the remaining provisions shall continue in full force and effect. All disputes arising in respect of usage of this website, shall be governed by the laws of Germany. SPECS hereby reserves the right to change its website at any time.Legal EffectThis Disclaimer of liability is part of SPECS‘s website. If any term or phrase of this Disclaimer should not comply with current law, then such term or phrase shall be severed from the remainder of this Disclaimer, and such remainder shall continue in full force and effect.Contact UsWe will be happy to answer any questions you may have regarding this Policy. Please contact us using the following contact details: For questions on our website or the handling of your personal data, please write an email to our webmaster: Andreas Thissen, SPECS GmbH, Voltastr. 5, D-13355 Berlin, Germany Tel.: +49 30 46 78 24-0 Fax: +49 30 46 78 083 Email: andreas.thissen@specs.com For questions or complaints about data protection please direct your communication to: Data Protection Officer, SPECS GmbH, Voltastr. 5, D-13355 Berlin, Germany Tel.: +49 30 46 78 24-0 Fax: +49 30 46 42 083 Email: info@specs.com © Copyright 23.05.2018 SPECS Surface Nano Analysis GmbH
Your web browser is deprecated
This could effect the presentation and some functions of our website.
Ok
